A Guide to the Rockefeller University records, Student Life and Activities FA842
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University records, Student Life and Activities
1963-1986
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller University
Acheson, N. H.
Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
FA842
0.44 Cubic Feet 1 box
1 box.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be closed to research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be closed to researchers at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/Head of Reference.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Material received by Mrs. Ruth Sternfeld, folders 1-8, and additions.
File Plan note
Former Classification: I 465
Conditions Governing Access note
This collection is open for scholarly research.
Medical technology; Arboviruses; Medical research; Cell and biomolecular sciences; Medicine, Preventive; Medical sciences; Biochemistry; Chemistry; Medical education; Science -- Study and teaching; Animal behavior; Biology -- Research; Life sciences; Rockefeller University; Acheson, N. H.; Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research
- R.U. Chess Club (R.U.C.C.) and Bulletin (B.R.U.C.C.)
  Scope and Contents note
  Photocopies from George Barany.
  - 1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Student Representative Committee, circa 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
  Correspondence and ballots, ca 1970, re possible appointment of student to RU Board of Trustees.
- Miscellaneous papers (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Gwyn Ballard and Norman Kagan circular letter, re temporary home for stray dog "Prince" with annotated note by Rollin D. Hotchkiss, 1977 July 28
  - Sandra R. Simon, outline of course work, undated; copy
  - Faculty and Students Club (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Annual Reports, 1963-1964 1964-1965 1966-1967
    - Minutes of Annual Meeting of Board of Directors, 1966 December 29
    - Invitations to "gala evenings", 1975
- Nina Felice Tabachnik Schor, "To the East of Ever After" [Booklet of poetry], 1986 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Gift of Robert H. and Nina Tabachnik Schor, via S.W. Mirsky.